So it doesn't show up, after all.
Machines are no good, then.
Only living creatures can perceive them.
It seems I'll need humans to help me find them.
It's okay, don't worry.
The inhabitants of this
planet are all good people.
I'm sure they'll find you.
This is a total Sunday.
What makes it a "total" Sunday?
Can you explain?
What's your problem? I was only trying
to create a relaxing mood for you.
I don't need a relaxing mood.
Let's just get started.
Fine then. You're so impatient.
Whaaaa--!
Huh?
Why are you taking your clothes off?!
Why? I'm about to get inside of you.
You brought it up...
Why do I transform? And what
do the coins have to do with it?
You said you wanted to know.
But if we're going to go down that path,
it means we might run into
another monster like that girl.
That's why we need to figure out exactly what
we're capable of together,
right now, while we can.
If you're in, hurry up and
turn into the doggy, all right?
I mean, I will, but-- Doggy?
I'm still not sure why you
have to take your clothes off.
Oh, this?
Honestly, Shuichi...
Your insides are stuffy as hell.
You are a costume, after all.
If it was winter, it'd be nice and warm.
But right now it's summer.
My underwear will get
totally drenched with sweat.
And they'll get your slimy liquid all over them.
Yeah, but still,
getting inside of me naked is...
Don't worry about it!
We've already gone that far once, anyway.
What do you mean, "gone that far"?!
Let's become one.
No!
Ugh, this is so lame.
Th-That should be fine, right?
It's no problem if a swimsuit gets wet,
and it's easy to wash.
I can't believe you'd rather have me
wear a school swimsuit than be naked.
I guess everyone has a fetish.
That's not what this is about!
Okay, you ready?
Yeah...
Yep, there's still nothing there. Empty.
Oh.
All right, I'm coming in.
It's okay, Shuichi.
Just relax. I'll be gentle.
This feeling... It's the same as before.
I feel her inside of me so clearly.
I can feel your anxiety.
It's just like it was my own body.
It's weird, but I feel like I could move
in ways I'd never be able to normally.
How is it for you?
Can you move by yourself?
Let me try.
Wow, my body is being moved! Gross.
It feels gross for me, too.
All right, Shuichi.
Can you grab that cup over there?
Yeah, no problem.
What the hell? My body won't--
I'm stopping you.
What?!
It looks like I have more
control over movement than you.
Okay, I'll take the left hand,
you take the right,
and we'll see who can grab the cup the fastest.
Got it.
All right. Ready? Go!
Tickle tickle tickle!
What-- Clair, stop it, I--
Come on little guy, come on!
Oh, not there!
Here? How's here?
That's better.
I knew you had a fetish, weirdo.
Shuichi, could you grab one
of the things in the fridge for me?
Okay.
Are you keeping these cold?
Huh? It's good during the summer.
All right, on to the next problem.
Problem?
My sister's school uniform is in there.
I noticed when I first went inside of you--
You have a powerful sense of smell.
Even in the dark,
I could tell where everything was;
the same as though it was right before my eyes.
Not only that, you can smell things
that are nowhere near you,
and distinguish smells
well enough to follow people.
With that nose, we can find my sister.
This might be my personal goal,
but seeing as how we have
no other information on these monsters,
finding her will be very valuable for you, too.
Clair's sister...
Clair said she killed their parents,
then disappeared.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Did you actually see
your sister kill your parents?
I didn't. But...
Six months ago, I came home from school,
and our house was in shambles.
Standing there was a monster
that seemed like my sister.
Elena... Is that you?
That's right.
And next to her were my parents' corpses.
Isn't that enough circumstantial evidence?
I can sense Clair's feelings, if only slightly.
Is she feeling anxious? Lost?
Or does she still feel that her sister--
Shuichi.
I understand. That's right. I need to know...
Why I take this form.
Why that person attacked me.
And... The reason for the crime we committed.
That smell...
The smell of blood!
And it's not just one or two people...
How many lives were lost?!
I've been naïve.
It doesn't matter whether Clair saw it or not.
It's completely clear.
The one that killed Clair's parents...
...was this beast!
Well, I thought I was prepared for this.
But it looks like the situation
is worse than I expected.
Shuichi, what will you do?
Look for her. Together.
Hello, welcome.
Food, water. And a memory card.
Oh, right! Should we get a portable toilet?
I've never been on a stakeout
before, so I don't know.
I don't think we need that.
Well, in the worst case,
I can just use a plastic bottle.
You think two per person is enough?
What?!
Oh, uh... Nothing.
Thank you.
Would you like me to heat this up?
Uh, yeah, please.
Can you heat that up too?
Open it up first though, please.
All right.
You said you liked it cold earlier.
The maple flavor is better when you heat it up.
Aren't you going to eat?
That smell, it's still...
But we can't do our stakeout if you don't eat.
Yeah, I guess.
Honestly though, I'm surprised.
When you smelled
my sister's scent, even I felt fear--
But you still said you wanted
to look for her, together.
Are you trying to say that's not like me?
Not at all. It was cool of you.
Clair.
What?
What are you planning
to do if we find your sister?
Hmm. I just want to ask her...
Why she turned into a monster.
Why she killed our mom and dad.
And...
And?
Never mind. Nothing.
What about you? What's your family like?
My family? I guess we don't
spend a lot of time together.
My parents are always working
and aren't home much.
And I was also sent to cram school.
Still, we're pretty much normal...
So I'd like to get tangled up
in all this as little as possible.
Oh.
Oh!
What is it?
Oh... Nothing.
Well, this is the third day.
Lots of people use this station,
and my sister's school is nearby, but...
We've picked up nothing so far.
Maybe my intuition was off.
Shuichi, give me some water!
We're out.
I suspect my sister is still in this town.
She might be a beast,
but it's still hard for a high schooler
to live alone in a town
where she doesn't know anyone.
You think someone is helping her?
That's my guess.
But if someone has been in contact with her,
that person should have her scent on them.
And if the scent is there,
your nose should pick it up. Right?
That's right. I've got to find it.
This is the only clue we have
that might reveal my secret.
Even if we are after a beast...
Yes...
I will find her!
That's right! We'll get that slut together!
What?! Is your sister a slut?
Huh? Well, I don't actually know.
By the way, I'm a virgin!
I wasn't asking!
Well, I guess we should wrap it up.
Want to try looking at the mall tomorrow?
There are a lot of people there, too.
The mall, huh?
What is it?
Nothing. I just remembered there's
a movie playing that I want to see.
Sorry, it's not important.
We've got other things to think about.
Let's go. I don't want
to see a scary movie, though.
I'm not good with scary movies.
Are you sure you want to go?
We need some time to relax, too.
What happened? You transformed out of nowhere!
Someone's here.
So, you found someone who smells
like my sister. Is it a boy? A girl?
A girl. On the platform.
If it's a girl, it must be one of her classmates.
Not there.
What is this smell?
Even from this far away... Just breathing in...
Seems to weigh me down...
No good, Shuichi.
That's not my sister's classmate.
That...
Is my sister herself.
That... is Clair's sister?!
Let's go, Shuichi.
Hang on, Clair! What are we going to do?
Isn't it obvious? We're going to capture her.
Capture her?
First, we'll shoot her
with your gun, so she can't move.
Shoot her? Just like that?
Shuichi. She's killed many people.
She's a murderous demon.
But she's your sister!
So what?
So... Let me do it, alone!
No.
What?!
Did you forget? I thought I told you...
We two are one.
Okay, Shuichi. We've only got one chance.
Clair... Are you sure
you can't just talk to her?
You two are sisters!
Talk to the person who killed our parents?
We'll aim for her legs. I'll fire the gun.
Huh?
After she goes down, hit her and knock her out.
Then we'll run off with her.
How...?
How can she stay so calm?
She's about to meet the person
who killed her parents...
About to shoot her own sister!
I don't feel any emotion coming from her.
She's erased them...
Completely...
Erased all her feelings!
No!
I can't move.
She's touching me... I can feel it...
I am nothing compared to her!
I can't believe you'd just shoot me like that.
No! She'll kill--
Oh... It's... I'm sorry.
I'm not used to this. So... You see...
Sorry... I need time to think...
Oh no, what should I do here?!
What should I talk about?!
Oh god! He can totally tell
I have communication problems!
What should I do?!
Wh-What the hell is with her?
I-It's okay. I understand.
You've come to kill me, haven't you?
Um, but, would you mind
if we do it somewhere else?
You know, somewhere it
won't bother other people?
What the hell is with her?
She's nothing like the picture,
or Clair's description.
Is she really a murderous demon?
But... How did you find me?
Did someone tell you?
Oh, I'm sorry!
It's nothing for you to worry about.
I'm talking too much again.
I feel like I can talk to her.
She's not attacking us
like the last girl we faced.
We even fired a gun at her,
and she's still so reserved!
I understand why you're
trying to kill me. Completely.
And I know who you are, too.
Yes. It's all my fault.
She noticed? She could tell
that I was inside of Shuichi?
I was weak. And that's why
you got wrapped up in this.
That's why... I don't mind if you kill me.
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry, Shuichi!
I'm the one who made you take that form.
What are you saying...?
Wait... That sounded...
That sounded like... a girl's voice.
Is there a girl inside of you right now?!
Filthy!
Disgusting!
Get out of there!
That place...
...belongs to me!
"Episode 4: I Wish I Was Someone Else"